Torch Mood Environment Now let's just connect you and
ask them what situation they see
on the chart. Kanwar Sahib was
discussing calcium and you said that folding 15600 650 is
very important. He turned around and
came back to this. Did you gain some
confidence that Shakkar Khedi Sarpanch
250 that he got rid of yesterday and today as well. Now
I think the active space created became 15500
10. There was a check bounce. Then
looking at the structural texture of the market, there was some
compromise because
this rise has become a high road phase and
send around 100 53526 side. But the entire
planning comes on the flu. These drops, perhaps, it should be understood.
This place should be looked at in two ways.
Duty with soil and negative pack.
Now it seems that it is reactive, liver is needed for possible
and
that we can do 15750, but the problem is to
put a stop in it. This carat
is not a plan, but when I look at the policy bank, it
seems that a plate is being
formed here.  And here anger and flavour
also stops it. If you get something like this in Bank Nifty, then there
is a possibility of it going up to 3000. By tomorrow, the twin of stroke
which is 30.20 250, so according to hips and repair 19,
a special spread is formed here, there is a
pack inside,
so the Mithi Bank Ware basically can be done by clocking a
trader, the target will be 1535 500.
If you
were giving position of this committee, well, how will you
choose the stop this hour, do you have any idea about the bullishness
in your hand, of course I had two
attempts in the morning, you got good results
in one and in the other one you
started, I will tell you the names of both, one
is ICICI General Insurance, it
seems you should do it, there is support at the level of 2019, in this you will
get more, I
see a target of 1520, this is the first target, you will
see more tears, the second object
was admitted there and that is Bharti Airtel, you should make
its target 570, it is very good.  It
is boiled but it will have to be modified,
I will cook it for 10 minutes
for five to eight days and the stop will remain the same, if it is
5.64 then we will make it 550 and some tips,
both the stop and target will have to be modified,
you will get it in Indian, it will go up to 500
and there will be more losses in both which you
will see in the party